Now, what is of interest to us about this project is the features which make the building energy-efficient.
现在，让我们对这个项目感兴趣的是建筑的节能特色。
Sunlight floods in through the glass wall,and to maximise it there are lots of mirrors and windows inside the house.
阳光透过玻璃墙射入，通过屋里的许多镜子和窗户将阳光最大化。
That helps to spread the light around.So that's the first thing - light is utilised as fully as possible.
这有助于光线的扩散。所以这是第一点，尽可能全面的使用光亮。
In addition, the special tiles on the outside convert energy from the sun and generate some of the house's electricity.
另外，外面的特殊瓷砖可以转化太阳能，为房子供电。
In fact, and it's possible that in future the house may even generate an electricity surplus,
事实上，房子在未来甚至可能产生剩余的电力，
and that the owners will be able to sell some to the nationa grid.
房主可以把一些电力卖给国家电网。
As well as that, wherever possible, recycled materials have been used.For example, the floors are made of reclaimed wood.
除此之外，只要有可能，用得都是回收的材料。例如，地板用得是回收木材。
And the owners haven't bought a single item of new fumiture - they just kept what they already had.
而且房主没买一件新家具，他们依旧用过去的。
And then there's the system for dealing with the waste produced in the house.
之后，房子里有一个处理垃圾的系统。
This is dealt with organically - it's purified by being filtered through reed beds which have been planted for that purpose in the garden.
这是有机化处理，它通过芦苇地被净化了，这就是在花园里种它们的用途。
So the occupants of the house won't pollute the land or use any damaging chemicals.
所以房子的居住者不会污染土地或使用任何有害的化学物质。
It's true that the actual construction of the house was harmful to the environment,
房屋的建造确实会对环境造成危害，
mainly because they had to use massive amounts of concrete - one of the biggest sources of carbon dioxide in manufacturing.
主要是因为他们不得不使用大量的混凝土，这是制造业中二氧化碳最大的来源之一。
And, as you know, this is very damaging to the environment.
正如你知道的，这对环境非常有害。
In total, the house construction has released 70 tons of carbon dioxide into the air.
房屋建造总共向空气中释放了70吨的二氧化碳。
Now that's a frightening thought.
这是一种令人恐惧的想法。
However, once the initial 'debt' has been cleared - cost anything - environmentally I mean - because unlike ordinary houses,
然而，一旦最初的“债”被还清了，据统计这只需要15年的时间。这所地下房屋对环境不会造成任何代价，
it is run in a way that is completely environmentally friendly.
因为它与普通住房不同，它完全对生态环境无害。
So, eco-housing like this is likely to become much more...
所以，这种生态住房可能变得更加……